[{"answer": "Yes, Piers.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Ben Wedeman, can you hear me?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, at the moment, I think people are really bracing for the possibility that certainly after hearing that rather incoherent but threatening speech from Libyan leader Moammar Gadhafi that he may be trying to launch some sort of counteroffensive against the eastern part of the country.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "What is going on there right now?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Well, I think they do.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Do you think -- do they believe, as the Egyptian people believed, that they can actually get rid of Gadhafi finally?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Well, he still has a fairly sizable air force.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "What's he potentially able to do?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Hef.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What do you like to be called?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Very exciting.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "What do you make of what we're seeing now?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "And you Tweet, of course?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, it is the purest form of democracy.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "But it's fascinating to see so many of these young people in the Middle East taking on these old dictators and bringing them down through sheer force of, we want change, isn't it?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I think it will be -- you know, I don't think there's a simple answer to that.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Do you think it's the end of these old kind of dictatorial ruling families around the world who are fleecing their own people?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, I think we need to get back to fundamentals in terms of -- you know, both conceptually and economically.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "What's the answer for America, do you think?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Well, one of the things I would be thinking about -- I mean what's happened, of course, is that we've outsourced half of our businesses, and national boundaries don't have a lot of meaning anymore.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "What's back to basics?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "There's no future in that.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "\"Playboy\" sells around the world, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "We are one of the most famous brand in China.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Do you have any sales in places like China at the moment or not?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "On the mainland of China where the magazine is not yet permitted, we are one of the most famous menswear brands.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "So you sell the merchandise, but you can't sell the magazine?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "It can't be long before \"Playboy\" is allowed to be on sale?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Man, you're asking the wrong guy in terms of that.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "What's the fast way that Obama can try and sort this?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, not only do we need to put people to work, we need to become more sophisticated in terms of technology.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Do you think it's forgotten what it did so magnificently 40, 50 years ago?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "That was fun.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "How excited do you sound in that video?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Yes --", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Hef, what do you possibly see in Crystal?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "What indeed?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Here's the ring.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Can I see the ring?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, I've just -- just literally, you know, it's fate, obviously.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "You could have had any woman in the world -- you've had most of them, so how did you -- how did you narrow it down to Crystal?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "The date of the wedding.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "You're going to reveal the date of the wedding?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Can I tell him?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, it was on Christmas Eve.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "And how did you propose, Hef?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I love Hef.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "What's the magic of Hugh Hefner?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Groucho Marx I think said, you're only as old as the woman you feel.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "How long does the average marriage last?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "I do think -- yes, I think without question, a relationship with somebody younger does keep you alive, absolutely.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "I mean, do you feel young ladies keep you feeling young?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I was faithful -- I was married -- my last marriage, which was not successful, I was faithful to it.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Could you imagine being faithful to her?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "So you actually are going to be genuine faithful to Crystal?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "They still come around, every weekend.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "So what happens to all the other women in the mansion?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "They're not allowed upstairs.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "But they're not allowed anymore to partake?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, you never know.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "So you've hung up your sword, for want of a better phrase?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "I don't know what to say.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "But you honestly believe Hef will not have sex with any other woman ever again other than you?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "So as long as she goes along with it, it's fine?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "No, no, we don't talk about politics.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "I mean do you talk about politics much with Hef, I'd imagine?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Yes, we watch it.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Do you ever watch that?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "You have?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "How am I doing?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, I have a lower back problem which I got in the wars.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "What other sort of war wounds do you have?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I mean, I think he looks great at all ages.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "I suppose, Crystal, when you look at the young Hef, I mean do you kind of wish that you were with him when he was that age?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I wish that we would have met earlier.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "When you see yourself back in those firebrand days?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Essentially, yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "So you always try and stay friends with them all?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Some have been kind --", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Have they all taken news of the engagement well, or has there been a little bit of (INAUDIBLE) tension?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Anger and some not quite so kind.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Some tension?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Who's taken it the worst, Crystal, would you say?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Holly -- Holly, OK about it?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Where Holly was, you mean?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I don't know what the number was.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "What was the tally then?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Is there anything -- is there anything more important to your life than sex?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, I think that perhaps love, friendship.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't want to try it without.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "And how much is you -- I don't want to be personal but how much is your ability to continue having a good sex life down to the wonder drug Viagra?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Everything.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "What do you guys talk about?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, almost everything.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "What do you talk about?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Well, actually, that's a damned good question.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Did you do this?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "She was actually on my -- in my brother's acting class in New York,.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Did you know Marilyn Monroe?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "She was a remarkable -- Dennis Hopper was in that class too, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Well, it's fairly well structured.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "For you two, when you get married, what will be a classic normal day?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly didn't do it alone.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "How much of the \"Playboy\" brand, do you think, is down to you, personally?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "My parents were very puritan, Nebraska farm people.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "You didn't even lose your virginity until you were in your 20s?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Well, they were around long enough to see what it was all about.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "What would they have made of the empire you've built?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "She got it all back, many, many times over.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "To get it all going?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "I wanted to create a lifestyle magazine.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What did you want to achieve with the brand?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "He still is, right?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Yeah!", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "He's always been a bit of a naughty boy, hasn't he?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "It's true.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "ARRIS: I have Bieber fever.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Bieber wants to come to the playboy mansion?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "He'll do all right.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "What's going to happen to him?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I think that's the idea.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Is that the point of these parties?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "I've walked in on a couple of people in the game house.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Can people go there and have sex non grata and things?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "He's going to bring his father.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Is this going to be a healthy place for Justin Bieber to find himself?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "I think that's the key.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Do you want to grow up?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Cooper, how are you?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "I mean, it is what it is.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "But it is a bit weird, isn't it?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "I knew you were going to ask that too.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "What's it like being Hugh Hefner's son?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "It's -- again, I don't have anything else to base it off of.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Am I that predictable?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "He's a good dad.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "What kind of dad is he?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "He's a fantastic son.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "How's he done?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "You must be very popular with your band mates?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "A young teenager, maybe?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Could you imagine going into the business?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "We've talked about it.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "Do you think you will?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "We have fun.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "I mean, what else do you ask for besides wanting your parents to be happy?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "Well, I have a girlfriend.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "What is life like in the mansion for you?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "It's good.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "If you could sum it up in one word, what would you say?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "I grew very much influenced by the movies.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "Why was it important to you, the Hollywood sign?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "EFNER: There's a song Sinatra did.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "How old would you like to see?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "Do you worry about dying?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "It's good.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 771, "question": "And it's good?", "qSentId": 770}, {"answer": "Never been better.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "Life's pretty good right now?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "Well, it all began with Marilyn Monroe.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "Of all the pin-ups you've ever had in the history of \"Playboy,\" what's been your personal favorite?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "It would have to be.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "Would that be your favorite?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "I think she's the major sex star of the 20th century.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "Do you think she was the greatest pin up of them all?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "I stopped counting a while back.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "And you bought that picture for 500 dollars and it became a business that's worth -- what are you worth now?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 788, "question": "Can I guess?", "qSentId": 787}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "But you're north of 100 million dollars, right?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "It has to do with adapting.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 802, "question": "Or have you been able to adapt to changing dynamics?", "qSentId": 801}, {"answer": "As somebody who had some positive impact on changing the social sexual values of his time.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "What would you like you epitaph to say?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "The same.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 822, "question": "How do you think you'll be remembered?", "qSentId": 821}, {"answer": "I think that he's done incredible things.", "docId": "110222pmt", "aSentId": 828, "question": "When push comes to shove and you have to assess him as a cultural figure in America, how do you think he'll rate?", "qSentId": 827}]